[
 {
  "S.N.": 1,
  "Question": "Capital of Nepal ?",
  "Option A": "Pokhara",
  "Option B": "Lumbini",
  "Option C": "Dang",
  "Option D": "Kathmandu",
  "Correct Answer": "Kathmandu",
  "Explanation": "Ktm is Capital"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 2,
  "Question": "A for apple, B for --------?",
  "Option A": "Dog",
  "Option B": "Cat",
  "Option C": "Ball",
  "Option D": "Elephant",
  "Correct Answer": "Ball",
  "Explanation": "Bhakundo"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 3,
  "Question": "soil is --------- ?",
  "Option A": "Incompressible",
  "Option B": "Consolidated ",
  "Option C": "Three phase",
  "Option D": "Soild ",
  "Correct Answer": "Three phase",
  "Explanation": "Basic Rule"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 4,
  "Question": "Mooram is ?",
  "Option A": "Air",
  "Option B": "Soil",
  "Option C": "Water",
  "Option D": "None",
  "Correct Answer": "Soil",
  "Explanation": "Basic Rule"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 5,
  "Question": "Capital of Nepal ?",
  "Option A": "Pokhara",
  "Option B": "Lumbini",
  "Option C": "Dang",
  "Option D": "Kathmandu",
  "Correct Answer": "Kathmandu",
  "Explanation": "Ktm is Capital"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 6,
  "Question": "A for apple, B for --------?",
  "Option A": "Dog",
  "Option B": "Cat",
  "Option C": "Ball",
  "Option D": "Elephant",
  "Correct Answer": "Ball",
  "Explanation": "Bhakundo"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 7,
  "Question": "Fe is --- ?",
  "Option A": 230,
  "Option B": 250,
  "Option C": 425,
  "Option D": 500,
  "Correct Answer": 500,
  "Explanation": "Yeti pani audaina ?"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 8,
  "Question": "Stress is ?",
  "Option A": "Force\/Length",
  "Option B": "Force\/Breadth",
  "Option C": "Force\/Area",
  "Option D": "F\/ma",
  "Correct Answer": "Force\/Area",
  "Explanation": "Basic Rule"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 9,
  "Question": "Sum of Fx = ? For equillibrium ?",
  "Option A": 1,
  "Option B": 0,
  "Option C": 100,
  "Option D": "Infinity",
  "Correct Answer": 0,
  "Explanation": "Basic Rule"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 10,
  "Question": "What is 15*365 ?",
  "Option A": 32423,
  "Option B": 34534,
  "Option C": 5475,
  "Option D": 2342,
  "Correct Answer": 5475,
  "Explanation": "Basic Rule"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 11,
  "Question": "What is 6 + 20198 ?",
  "Option A": 323424,
  "Option B": 20204,
  "Option C": 234324,
  "Option D": 23234,
  "Correct Answer": 20204,
  "Explanation": "Basic Rule"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 12,
  "Question": "36435*231361 = ?",
  "Option A": 8429638035,
  "Option B": 3213234123,
  "Option C": 34123423,
  "Option D": 342421425,
  "Correct Answer": 8429638035,
  "Explanation": "Multiply last digits"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 13,
  "Question": "Determinant of Zero matrix is ?",
  "Option A": 1,
  "Option B": 2,
  "Option C": 3,
  "Option D": 0,
  "Correct Answer": 0,
  "Explanation": "Zero is rule."
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 14,
  "Question": "What is 16*3 ?",
  "Option A": 33,
  "Option B": 122,
  "Option C": 48,
  "Option D": 32,
  "Correct Answer": 48,
  "Explanation": "Basic Rule"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 15,
  "Question": "What is 6 + 20198 ?",
  "Option A": 323424,
  "Option B": 20204,
  "Option C": 234324,
  "Option D": 23234,
  "Correct Answer": 20204,
  "Explanation": "Basic Rule"
 },
 {
  "S.N.": 16,
  "Question": "36435*231361 = ?",
  "Option A": 8429638035,
  "Option B": 3213234123,
  "Option C": 34123423,
  "Option D": 342421425,
  "Correct Answer": 8429638035,
  "Explanation": "Multiply last digits"
 }
]